[{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 1",
    "question": "The hip is formed from the fusion of 3 bones, which are:",
    "answers": ["b"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "ilium, sacrum and femur",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Ilium, ischium and pubis",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "sacrum, pubis and femur",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "sacrum, acetabulum and fibula",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 2",
    "question": "The sacrum is formed by the fusion of how many vertebrae?",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "2 vertebrae",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "3 vertebrae",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "4 vertebrae",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "5 vertebrae",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 3",
    "question": "The coccyx is formed by the fusion of how many vertebrae?",
    "answers": ["c"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "2 vertebrae",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "3 vertebrae",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "3-5 vertebrae",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "5 vertebrae",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 4",
    "question": "In adults, the bone pelvis is formed by how many bones?",
    "answers": ["b"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "2 bones",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "4 bones",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "6 bones",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "8 bones",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 5",
    "question": "The sacrococcygeal joint is responsible for connecting:",
    "answers": ["a"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Apex of the sacrum at the base of the coccyx",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Base of the sacrum at the apex of the coccyx",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Center of the sacrum to the side of the coccyx",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Lateral sacrum at the base of the coccyx",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 6",
    "question": "Sacroiliac ligaments limit pelvis movement in:",
    "answers": ["b"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Adduction and flexion",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Rotation and sliding",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Adduction and abduction",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Rotation and abduction",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 7",
    "question": "From the following movements, it is not possible to see the pelvis performing:",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Retroversion",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Rotation",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Anteroversion",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Flexion",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 8",
    "question": "Of the following muscles, which is not part of the pelvic wall?",
    "answers": ["b"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Coccygeal muscle",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Deltoid muscle",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Internal obturator muscle",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Piriform muscle",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 9",
    "question": "Of the nerves below, which is not part of the pelvic innervation?",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Pudendal Nerve",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Sciatic Nerve",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Pelvic splanchnic nerve",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Femoral Nerve",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 10",
    "question": "Of the following arteries, which is not part of the pelvic vascularization?",
    "answers": ["c"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Umbilical artery",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Uterine artery",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Lower mesenteric artery",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Obturator artery",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 11",
    "question": "Of the urinary organs below, which is not present in the pelvic cavity?",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Urethra",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Urinary bladder",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Ureters",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Kidneys",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 12",
    "question": "The pelvis is divided into:",
    "answers": ["c"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Medial pelvis and central pelvis",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Major pelvis (false), and minor pelvis (true)",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Real pelvis and false pelvis",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Upper and lower pelvis",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 13",
    "question": "What is the location of the perineum compartment?",
    "answers": ["c"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Above the upper opening of the pelvis",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Below the upper pelvis opening",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Below the lower pelvis opening",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Above the lower pelvis opening",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 14",
    "question": "Of the following osteofibrous structures, which does not mark the limits of the perineum?",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Sciatic tubers",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Pubic symphysis",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Sacrotuberous ligaments",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "External sphincter of the anus",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 15",
    "question": "The perineum body is the place of convergence of several muscles, which are:",
    "answers": ["a"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Bulb-responsive, external sphincter of the anus and transverse superficial and deep of the perineum",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Internal, coccygeal and piriform shutter",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Bulb-responsive, coccygeal and external sphincter of the anus",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Internal, bulbous and piriform shutter",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 16",
    "question": "The anal canal is vascularized by:",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Superior rectal artery, vesical artery and median rectal artery",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Bladder artery and rectal arteries",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Bladder artery, medial rectal artery and uterine artery",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Superior rectal artery, inferior rectal arteries and middle rectal arteries",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 17",
    "question": "The anal canal is reversed by:",
    "answers": ["b"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Lower rectal nerves and superior rectal nerve",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Lower hypogastric plexus and lower rectal nerves",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Lower rectal nerves and pudendal nerve",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Lower hypogastric plexus and pudendal nerve",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 18",
    "question": "The masculine perineum includes:",
    "answers": ["c"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Root of the penis, testicles and scrotum",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Anal canal, penis and testicles",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Anal canal, root of the penis and scrotum and part of the urethra",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Root of the penis, prostate and scrotum",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 19",
    "question": "The female perineum is limited by:",
    "answers": ["b"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Anal canal, intergluteal cleft and large lips",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Monte do pubis, medial thigh surfaces, infragluteal sulcus and intergluteal cleft",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Mount of pubis, anal canal and labia majora",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Anal canal, pubis mount and intergluteal cleft",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "pelve",
    "title": "Question 20",
    "question": "The external female genital organs are, respectively:",
    "answers": ["a"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Mount of pubis, labia majora, labia minora and clitoris",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Anal canal, vaginal canal, urethra and clitoris",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Vaginal canal, urethra and clitoris",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Mount of pubis, vaginal canal, small and large lips and clitoris",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
}
]